https://finzfirm.com/privacy-policy/

Skip Navigation
TapTo Call 855-TOP-FIRM
About Firm OverviewOur TeamPractice AreasAttorney ReferralsChanging Your AttorneyOur BlogNewsletterVideo LibraryScholarship – Devante LaneScholarship – Fighting InjusticeResultsTestimonialsAccidents Accidents OverviewBicycle AccidentsBus AccidentsCar AccidentsConstruction AccidentsDog BitesMotorcycle AccidentsPedestrian AccidentsPremises LiabilitySlip & Fall AccidentsTrain/Railroad AccidentsTruck AccidentsWorkplace AccidentsNew York Accident NewsAdditional Accident AreasMedical Malpractice Medical Malpractice OverviewAnesthesiology ErrorsBirth InjuriesCerebral PalsyFailure to DiagnoseHeart AttacksHospital MalpracticeMedication ErrorsMisdiagnosisNursing ErrorsOrthopedic MalpracticeRadiology ErrorsSurgical ErrorsAdditional Malpractice AreasProducts Liability Products Liability OverviewDefective Air BagsDefective DrugsDefective MachineryDefective Medical DevicesDefective Power ToolsDefective SeatbeltsDefective TiresSUV RolloversAdditional Product AreasInjury Topics AmputationsBrain InjuriesBurn InjuriesCOVID-19 Heroes FundCOVID-19 Nursing Home NeglectInfection & SepsisIV InfiltrationLead Paint ExposureNursing Home NeglectSpinal Cord InjuriesStroke InjuriesToxic ExposureWernicke’s EncephalopathyWrongful Death ClaimAdditional Injury AreasContact
About Firm OverviewOur TeamPractice AreasAttorney ReferralsChanging Your AttorneyOur BlogNewsletterVideo LibraryScholarship – Devante LaneScholarship – Fighting InjusticeResultsTestimonialsAccidents Accidents OverviewBicycle AccidentsBus AccidentsCar AccidentsConstruction AccidentsDog BitesMotorcycle AccidentsPedestrian AccidentsPremises LiabilitySlip & Fall AccidentsTrain/Railroad AccidentsTruck AccidentsWorkplace AccidentsNew York Accident NewsAdditional Accident AreasMedical Malpractice Medical Malpractice OverviewAnesthesiology ErrorsBirth InjuriesCerebral PalsyFailure to DiagnoseHeart AttacksHospital MalpracticeMedication ErrorsMisdiagnosisNursing ErrorsOrthopedic MalpracticeRadiology ErrorsSurgical ErrorsAdditional Malpractice AreasProducts Liability Products Liability OverviewDefective Air BagsDefective DrugsDefective MachineryDefective Medical DevicesDefective Power ToolsDefective SeatbeltsDefective TiresSUV RolloversAdditional Product AreasInjury Topics AmputationsBrain InjuriesBurn InjuriesCOVID-19 Heroes FundCOVID-19 Nursing Home NeglectInfection & SepsisIV InfiltrationLead Paint ExposureNursing Home NeglectSpinal Cord InjuriesStroke InjuriesToxic ExposureWernicke’s EncephalopathyWrongful Death ClaimAdditional Injury AreasContact
Call 24/7 for a Free Case Review 855-TOP-FIRM
Home Privacy Policy
Resize Text
Headline Headline Headline
Translate
Share
Email
Facebook
Twitter
Linkedin
More
Print
Privacy Policy
Last updated January 30, 2020Thank you for choosing to be part of our community at Finz & Finz, P.C. (“Company”, “we”, “us”, or “our”). We are committed to protecting your personal information and your right to privacy. If you have any questions or concerns about our notice, or our practices with regards to your personal information, please contact us at info@finzfirm.com.When you visit our website https://finzfirm.com/, and use our services, you trust us with your personal information. We take your privacy very seriously. In this privacy notice, we seek to explain to you in the clearest way possible what information we collect, how we use it and what rights you have in relation to it. We hope you take some time to read through it carefully, as it is important. If there are any terms in this privacy notice that you do not agree with, please discontinue use of our Sites and our services.This privacy notice applies to all information collected through our website (such as https://finzfirm.com/), and/or any related services, sales, marketing or events (we refer to them collectively in this privacy notice as the “Services“).Please read this privacy notice carefully as it will help you make informed decisions about sharing your personal information with us.TABLE OF CONTENTSWHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?HOW DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION?WILL YOUR INFORMATION BE SHARED WITH ANYONE?DO WE USE COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES?DO WE USE GOOGLE MAPS?HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?HOW DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION SAFE?DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM MINORS?WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS?CONTROLS FOR DO-NOT-TRACK FEATURESDO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS HAVE SPECIFIC PRIVACY RIGHTS?DO WE MAKE UPDATES TO THIS POLICY?HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS POLICY?1. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?Information automatically collectedIn Short: Some information — such as IP address and/or browser and device characteristics — is collected automatically when you visit our Services.We automatically collect certain information when you visit, use or navigate the Services. This information does not reveal your specific identity (like your name or contact information) but may include device and usage information, such as your IP address, browser and device characteristics, operating system, language preferences, referring URLs, device name, country, location, information about how and when you use our Services and other technical information. This information is primarily needed to maintain the security and operation of our Services, and for our internal analytics and reporting purposes.Like many businesses, we also collect information through cookies and similar technologies.2. HOW DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION?In Short: We process your information for purposes based on legitimate business interests, the fulfillment of our contract with you, compliance with our legal obligations, and/or your consent.We use personal information collected via our Services for a variety of business purposes described below. We process your personal information for these purposes in reliance on our legitimate business interests, in order to enter into or perform a contract with you, with your consent, and/or for compliance with our legal obligations. We indicate the specific processing grounds we rely on next to each purpose listed below.We use the information we collect or receive:To send you marketing and promotional communications. We and/or our third party marketing partners may use the personal information you send to us for our marketing purposes, if this is in accordance with your marketing preferences. You can opt-out of our marketing emails at any time (see the “WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS” below).To send administrative information to you. We may use your personal information to send you product, service and new feature information and/or information about changes to our terms, conditions, and policies.To post testimonials. We post testimonials on our Services that may contain personal information. Prior to posting a testimonial, we will obtain your consent to use your name and testimonial. If you wish to update, or delete your testimonial, please contact us at info@finzfirm.com and be sure to include your name, testimonial location, and contact information.Deliver targeted advertising to you. We may use your information to develop and display content and advertising (and work with third parties who do so) tailored to your interests and/or location and to measure its effectiveness.For other Business Purposes. We may use your information for other Business Purposes, such as data analysis, identifying usage trends, determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns and to evaluate and improve our Services, products, marketing and your experience. We may use and store this information in aggregated and anonymized form so that it is not associated with individual end users and does not include personal information. We will not use identifiable personal information without your consent.3. WILL YOUR INFORMATION BE SHARED WITH ANYONE?In Short: We only share information with your consent, to comply with laws, to provide you with services, to protect your rights, or to fulfill business obligations.We may process or share data based on the following legal basis:Consent: We may process your data if you have given us specific consent to use your personal information in a specific purpose.Legitimate Interests: We may process your data when it is reasonably necessary to achieve our legitimate business interests.Performance of a Contract: Where we have entered into a contract with you, we may process your personal information to fulfill the terms of our contract.Legal Obligations: We may disclose your information where we are legally required to do so in order to comply with applicable law, governmental requests, a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process, such as in response to a court order or a subpoena (including in response to public authorities to meet national security or law enforcement requirements).Vital Interests: We may disclose your information where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding potential violations of our policies, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person and illegal activities, or as evidence in litigation in which we are involved.More specifically, we may need to process your data or share your personal information in the following situations:Vendors, Consultants and Other Third-Party Service Providers. We may share your data with third party vendors, service providers, contractors or agents who perform services for us or on our behalf and require access to such information to do that work. Examples include: payment processing, data analysis, email delivery, hosting services, customer service and marketing efforts. We may allow selected third parties to use tracking technology on the Services, which will enable them to collect data about how you interact with the Services over time. This information may be used to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content and better understand online activity. Unless described in this Policy, we do not share, sell, rent or trade any of your information with third parties for their promotional purposes.Business Transfers. We may share or transfer your information in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company.Third-Party Advertisers. We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Services. These companies may use information about your visits to our Website(s) and other websites that are contained in web cookies and other tracking technologies in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.Business Partners. We may share your information with our business partners to offer you certain products, services or promotions.4. DO WE USE COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES?In Short: We may use cookies and other tracking technologies to collect and store your information.We may use cookies and similar tracking technologies (like web beacons and pixels) to access or store information. Specific information about how we use such technologies and how you can refuse certain cookies is set out in our Cookie Policy.5. DO WE USE GOOGLE MAPS?In Short: Yes, we use Google Maps for the purpose of providing better service.This website, mobile application, or Facebook application uses Google Maps APIs. You may find the Google Maps APIs Terms of Service here. To better understand Google’s Privacy Policy, please refer to this link.By using our Maps API Implementation, you agree to be bound by Google’s Terms of Service.6. HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?In Short: We keep your information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this privacy notice unless otherwise required by law.We will only keep your personal information for as long as it is necessary for the purposes set out in this privacy notice, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law (such as tax, accounting or other legal requirements).When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will either delete or anonymize it, or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.7. HOW DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION SAFE?In Short: We aim to protect your personal information through a system of organizational and technical security measures.We have implemented appropriate technical and organizational security measures designed to protect the security of any personal information we process. However, please also remember that we cannot guarantee that the internet itself is 100% secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal information, transmission of personal information to and from our Services is at your own risk. You should only access the services within a secure environment.8. DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM MINORS?In Short: We do not knowingly collect data from or market to children under 18 years of age.We do not knowingly solicit data from or market to children under 18 years of age. By using the Services, you represent that you are at least 18 or that you are the parent or guardian of such a minor and consent to such minor dependent’s use of the Services. If we learn that personal information from users less than 18 years of age has been collected, we will deactivate the account and take reasonable measures to promptly delete such data from our records. If you become aware of any data we have collected from children under age 18, please contact us at info@finzfirm.com.9. WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS?In Short: You may review, change, or terminate your account at any time.If you are resident in the European Economic Area and you believe we are unlawfully processing your personal information, you also have the right to complain to your local data protection supervisory authority. You can find their contact details here: http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm.Cookies and similar technologies: Most Web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove cookies and to reject cookies. If you choose to remove cookies or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or services of our Services. To opt-out of interest-based advertising by advertisers on our Services visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices/.10. CONTROLS FOR DO-NOT-TRACK FEATURESMost web browsers and some mobile operating systems and mobile applications include a Do-Not-Track (“DNT”) feature or setting you can activate to signal your privacy preference not to have data about your online browsing activities monitored and collected. No uniform technology standard for recognizing and implementing DNT signals has been finalized. As such, we do not currently respond to DNT browser signals or any other mechanism that automatically communicates your choice not to be tracked online. If a standard for online tracking is adopted that we must follow in the future, we will inform you about that practice in a revised version of this privacy notice.11. DO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS HAVE SPECIFIC PRIVACY RIGHTS?In Short: Yes, if you are a resident of California, you are granted specific rights regarding access to your personal information.California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the “Shine The Light” law, permits our users who are California residents to request and obtain from us, once a year and free of charge, information about categories of personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared personal information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to us using the contact information provided below.If you are under 18 years of age, reside in California, and have a registered account with the Services, you have the right to request removal of unwanted data that you publicly post on the Services. To request removal of such data, please contact us using the contact information provided below, and include the email address associated with your account and a statement that you reside in California. We will make sure the data is not publicly displayed on the Services, but please be aware that the data may not be completely or comprehensively removed from our systems.12. DO WE MAKE UPDATES TO THIS POLICY?In Short: Yes, we will update this policy as necessary to stay compliant with relevant laws.We may update this privacy notice from time to time. The updated version will be indicated by an updated “Revised” date and the updated version will be effective as soon as it is accessible. If we make material changes to this privacy notice, we may notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to review this privacy notice frequently to be informed of how we are protecting your information.13. HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS POLICY?If you have questions or comments about this policy, you may email us at info@finzfirm.com or by post to:Finz & Finz, P.C.410 E Jericho TurnpikeMineola, NY 11501 United StatesHOW CAN YOU REVIEW, UPDATE, OR DELETE THE DATA WE COLLECT FROM YOU?Based on the laws of some countries, you may have the right to request access to the personal information we collect from you, change that information, or delete it in some circumstances. To request to review, update, or delete your personal information, please submit a request form by clicking here. We will respond to your request within 30 days.
Injured? Call Us Now855-TOP-FIRM(855-867-3476)ORTapClick For A Free Case Review
Our Results$24.5MillionTruck Accident Settlement$22.57MillionWrongful Death Verdict$20.52MillionDefective Product Verdict$14.76MillionWork Injury Verdict$9.75MillionBirth Injury SettlementView More Results
Meet Our Team
Stuart L. Finz
Hon. Leonard L. Finz
Cheri Finz
Todd M. Rubin
Jacquelin Finz
Brandon S. Finz
Meet Our Entire Team
Super Lawyers is a rating service of outstanding lawyers who have attained a high-degree of peer recognition and professional achievement. The selection process includes independent research, peer nominations and peer evaluations.
The Multi-Million Dollar Advocates Forum is one of the most prestigious groups of trial lawyers in the United States. Membership is limited to attorneys who have won million and multi-million dollar verdicts and settlements. Fewer than 1% of U.S. lawyers are members.
The National Trial Lawyers Top 100 is a professional organization composed of the top 100 trial lawyers from each state or highly-populated region of certain states who demonstrate superior qualifications, leadership skills and trial results. The selection process for this elite honor is based on a multi-phase process that includes peer nominations and third-party research.
Selection to America’s Top 100 High Stakes Litigators® is by invitation only and is reserved to identify the nation’s most exceptional trial attorneys in high value, high stakes legal matters.
AV Preeminent is the highest peer rating standard. This is given to attorneys who are ranked at the highest level of professional excellence for their legal expertise, communication skills, and ethical standards by their peers.
Attorney and Practice Magazine Top 10 Law Firm award is an achievement reserved for only those lawyers who have demonstrated the highest degree of excellence in his or her area of law. Because of our stringent standards, less than 1% of lawyers nationwide will receive this invitation for membership, subscription and list inclusion which is published on www.attorneyandpractice as well our quarterly magazine.
The New York Law Journal is the largest daily legal paper on NY law with focuses on banking and finance as well as analysis and case-winning intelligence.
The Bar Register of Preeminent Lawyers is the definitive guide to the most distinguished law firms in America. It includes only those select law practices that have earned the highest rating in the Martindale-Hubbell Law Directory and have been designated by their colleagues as preeminent in their field.
Connect With Us:
social-media-facebook-dark Created with Sketch.
social-media-Linkedin-dark Created with Sketch.
social-media-Youtube-dark Created with Sketch.
social-media-Twitter-dark Created with Sketch.
Long Island Office Finz & Finz, P.C.
410 East Jericho Turnpike
Mineola, NY 11501
Phone: (516) 433-3000 Toll Free: (855) TOP-FIRM
Directions More Info
Manhattan Office Finz & Finz, P.C.
One Penn Plaza
New York, NY 10119
Phone: (212) 513-1000 Toll Free: (855) TOP-FIRM
Directions More Info
Get a Free Case Review Tell Us About Your Case Referral Fill out the form and you will be contacted by our legal team.
Name*
Case Type*
Choose a Case Type Accident Medical Malpractice Defective Product Defective Drug Defective Medical Device Toxic Exposure Other
Email
Phone*
Incident Date
State
Choose a State Alabama Alaska Arizona Arkansas California Colorado Connecticut Delaware Florida Georgia Hawaii Idaho Illinois Indiana Iowa Kansas Kentucky Louisiana Maine Maryland Massachusetts Michigan Minnesota Mississippi Missouri Montana Nebraska Nevada New Hampshire New Jersey New Mexico New York North Carolina North Dakota Ohio Oklahoma Oregon Pennsylvania Puerto Rico Rhode Island South Carolina South Dakota Tennessee Texas Utah Vermont Virginia Washington Washington DC West Virginia Wisconsin Wyoming
Brief Description or Question
Send To Our Attorneys Back To Top
Helpful Links: Changing Your AttorneyAttorney ReferralsBlogAccident NewsCOVID-19 NewsContactPrivacy PolicyDisclaimerSite Map
Helpful Links:
Changing Your AttorneyAttorney ReferralsBlogAccident NewsCOVID-19 NewsContactPrivacy PolicyDisclaimerSite Map
© 2020 Finz & Finz, P.C. Personal Injury Law Firm - All Rights Reserved.
Back To Top
Office Hours
×
Weekends and evenings, by appointment.
